mafiadoc.com 2019-06-26

# Privacy Policy - MAFIADOC.COM

MAFIADOC.COM respects the privacy of its clients and visitors. We make every effort to protect the integrity of your personal information and the files you submit. Any personal information you enter into forms on our website will be encrypted to ensure it remains private. 

Our website collects names, email addresses, and other personal information from clients and potential clients only when submitted via one of our online forms, such as our Quote Request form. This data is used solely by MAFIADOC.COM and is not shared, traded, or sold to third parties. 

Clients can edit their personal information in Concourse by clicking on Manage Account, located in the upper right corner of each page when logged in. You can un-register at any time by writing to the email address above. 

Our website collects non-personal data through the use of server-based “session variables,” which we use to achieve important site functionality, including the recognition of logged-in users. 

Our web-server records IP addresses from all visitors to our site. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer when you use the Internet. We use IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer our site, to analyze trends, to track user movement, and to gather broad demographic information all for the purpose of continually improving our website and delivering personalized, custom content. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information, and their collection is standard procedure in most web-server environments. 

Our website contains links to other websites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are entering another website, for which MAFIADOC.COM is not responsible. 

Despite all efforts to protect your privacy and the confidentiality of the information you provide us, no computer system can be completely safe. Unscrupulous people continue to invent new ways to break security codes and steal information transmitted over the Internet. For this reason, we cannot guarantee that client confidentiality can always be maintained when using this website. We do, however, utilize extensive security measures to protect against loss, misuse or alteration of the information we receive. 

By using MAFIADOC.COM you signify your agreement to our privacy policy as stated above. Note that this policy may be revised periodically without notice. Please re-read this policy prior to submitting any personal information if you have concerns about how your information is being collected and used, and feel free to contact us if you have any questions.
